<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<addons><addon id="plugin.video.rivulet" name="Rivulet" version="0.4.20" provider-name="M0Rf30">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0" />
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.22.0" />
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup" />
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Rivulet: watch Stremio-protocol catalogs, addons and streams in Kodi</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Rivulet is a Kodi client for the Stremio addon protocol: browse Discover and Search catalogs, install community Stremio addons from a manifest URL, resolve streams and play them back through an embedded or remote stremio-server-go streaming server, and optionally sync your addon collection with your Stremio account.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">This addon does not host, index or provide any media content. It is a client for third-party Stremio addons that you install yourself.</disclaimer>
    <news>v0.4.20:
- New: README and the project site now show a real screenshot gallery of the current UI, generated by a new scripts/capture_screenshots.py (drives a running Kodi over its JSON-RPC socket).
- New: Kodi's own Add-ons browser now shows real screenshots for Rivulet instead of empty placeholders.
v0.4.19:
- Fix: quitting Kodi while the streaming-server binary was still auto-downloading no longer hangs shutdown until the download finishes.
- Fix: a crashed embedded server now releases its log file immediately on restart.
- Improved: stream resolution and Stremio account requests now reuse HTTP connections - snappier browsing and playback start on slow devices.
v0.4.18:
- Fix: Home screen's second line per row (e.g. "Browse catalogs from your installed addons" under Discover) was a hardcoded English literal that never translated, even when the row's own main label correctly did (e.g. "Scopri" in Italian). Now localized like every other string.
v0.4.17:
- New: Rivulet's UI is now translated - Italian, German, French, Spanish, Portuguese (Brazil), Dutch, Russian, Polish, Turkish, Chinese (Simplified), Japanese, Korean and Arabic, on top of English. The language follows Kodi's own interface-language setting automatically (Settings &gt; Interface &gt; Language), with no addon setting to configure.
v0.4.16:
- New: the embedded stremio-server's full configuration is now exposed under Settings (5 new sections: BitTorrent, Server resources, Server proxy, Server add-ons, Server diagnostics) - peer/tracker/encryption tuning, memory caps, idle-torrent timeout, proxy relay, Bitmagnet/Torznab indexers, DLNA casting and more, instead of only being controllable via environment variables. Changing any of them restarts the embedded server automatically, same as the existing Server URL setting already does.
v0.4.15:
- Fix: pressing Back from search results fell straight through to the Home menu instead of returning to the previous screen (Search had no screen of its own to return to).
- New: Search now remembers past queries (clearable) and lets you re-run one instead of retyping - Kodi's on-screen keyboard has no live-typing autocomplete, so this history list is the closest equivalent.
v0.4.14:
- Fix: Settings &gt; Account had no way to log in - clicking "Sync addons now" while logged out just said "Login to Stremio" with nowhere to do it. Added dedicated Login/Logout buttons there.
- Fix: the Kodi repository add-on used a schema Kodi 21+ no longer supports ("no directory matching" error) and could not be installed/updated on Kodi 21.
v0.4.13:
- New: a Kodi add-on repository (repository.rivulet) is now published, so Rivulet can update itself automatically instead of needing a manual zip reinstall for every release.
- New: a project site with install instructions and docs is published to GitHub Pages.
v0.4.12:
- New: Library and Add-ons now have their own custom screens (no more dropping to the classical Kodi directory).
- New: Add-ons screen lets you install from a manifest URL and remove addons directly.
- New: the streams screen shows year, runtime, rating and genres, and drops repeated provider names when every source is from the same addon.
- New: Discover's poster wall fades softly at both edges instead of a hard cut.
- Fix: backing out of a nested screen (Discover, a title's sources, ...) now correctly returns to the previous screen instead of sometimes jumping back to the Home menu.
v0.4.11:
- Fix: playback now takes the screen immediately - video no longer starts hidden behind the menu until you press Back.
- Fix: stopping playback no longer briefly spawns a duplicate Home screen.
v0.4.10:
- Fix: an addon that's briefly unavailable no longer freezes the UI - streams/search now query addons in parallel instead of one at a time.
- Fix: an expired Stremio session now prompts a clean re-login instead of silently failing.
- Fix: installed addons' info now refreshes automatically instead of going stale forever.
- Fix: a rare crash could leave a screen stuck open; screens now always close properly.
- Fix: two addon actions running at the same time could silently lose one of them - now safely retried.
- Security: the streaming server binary download now always verifies its integrity before installing.
v0.4.9:
- Fix: logging in no longer wipes addons you installed while logged out - addon sync is now a proper two-way sync.
- New: Settings &gt; Account &gt; "Sync addons now" to force and confirm a sync.
- New: a loading spinner (with progress and cancel) now shows during Search/Discover/Streams lookups instead of a frozen screen.
- Fix: the app icon's logo graphic is now properly centered.
v0.4.8:
- Fix: movies no longer show a pointless "Play" step - pick a movie and go straight to sources.
- Fix: a stray "[/B]" no longer shows on the top stream row.
- Fix: Library and Add-ons no longer fail to open from the new Home.
- Home menu got icons, short descriptions and a login-status line.
v0.4.7:
- New: a custom, non-standard Home/Discover/Search/Detail/Streams UI (Library/Add-ons/Settings still classic).
- Showcase now reports errors (notification + log) instead of failing silently.</news>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <website>https://github.com/rivulet-kodi/plugin.video.rivulet</website>
    <source>https://github.com/rivulet-kodi/plugin.video.rivulet</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-01.png</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-02.png</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-03.png</screenshot>
      <screenshot>resources/screenshots/screenshot-04.png</screenshot>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon><addon id="repository.rivulet" name="Rivulet Repository" version="1.0.1" provider-name="M0Rf30">
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.repository" name="Rivulet Repository">
    <dir>
      <info compressed="false">https://rivulet-kodi.github.io/plugin.video.rivulet/addons.xml</info>
      <checksum>https://rivulet-kodi.github.io/plugin.video.rivulet/addons.xml.md5</checksum>
      <datadir zip="true">https://rivulet-kodi.github.io/plugin.video.rivulet/</datadir>
    </dir>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Rivulet Repository</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Add this repository to Kodi to install Rivulet and receive automatic updates.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <website>https://github.com/rivulet-kodi/plugin.video.rivulet</website>
    <source>https://github.com/rivulet-kodi/plugin.video.rivulet</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon></addons>