<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.rivulet" name="Rivulet" version="0.4.11" provider-name="M0Rf30">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.22.0"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
    <provides>video</provides>
  </extension>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="service.py" start="startup"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Rivulet: watch Stremio-protocol catalogs, addons and streams in Kodi</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">Rivulet is a Kodi client for the Stremio addon protocol: browse Discover and Search catalogs, install community Stremio addons from a manifest URL, resolve streams and play them back through an embedded or remote stremio-server-go streaming server, and optionally sync your addon collection with your Stremio account.</description>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">This addon does not host, index or provide any media content. It is a client for third-party Stremio addons that you install yourself.</disclaimer>
    <news>v0.4.11:
- Fix: playback now takes the screen immediately - video no longer starts hidden behind the menu until you press Back.
- Fix: stopping playback no longer briefly spawns a duplicate Home screen.
v0.4.10:
- Fix: an addon that's briefly unavailable no longer freezes the UI - streams/search now query addons in parallel instead of one at a time.
- Fix: an expired Stremio session now prompts a clean re-login instead of silently failing.
- Fix: installed addons' info now refreshes automatically instead of going stale forever.
- Fix: a rare crash could leave a screen stuck open; screens now always close properly.
- Fix: two addon actions running at the same time could silently lose one of them - now safely retried.
- Security: the streaming server binary download now always verifies its integrity before installing.
v0.4.9:
- Fix: logging in no longer wipes addons you installed while logged out - addon sync is now a proper two-way sync.
- New: Settings > Account > "Sync addons now" to force and confirm a sync.
- New: a loading spinner (with progress and cancel) now shows during Search/Discover/Streams lookups instead of a frozen screen.
- Fix: the app icon's logo graphic is now properly centered.
v0.4.8:
- Fix: movies no longer show a pointless "Play" step - pick a movie and go straight to sources.
- Fix: a stray "[/B]" no longer shows on the top stream row.
- Fix: Library and Add-ons no longer fail to open from the new Home.
- Home menu got icons, short descriptions and a login-status line.
v0.4.7:
- New: a custom, non-standard Home/Discover/Search/Detail/Streams UI (Library/Add-ons/Settings still classic).
- Showcase now reports errors (notification + log) instead of failing silently.</news>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>MIT</license>
    <website>https://github.com/M0Rf30/plugin.video.rivulet</website>
    <source>https://github.com/M0Rf30/plugin.video.rivulet</source>
    <assets>
      <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
      <fanart>resources/fanart.jpg</fanart>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>
